https://www.swissix.ch/about/privacy-policy

Toggle navigation
HomeAssociationBoard and ManagementMembersMembership applicationParticipationParticipantsParticipants SCIONGet connectedSite specific notesConnection AgreementConnection Agreement AppendixPeering PolicyEquipment Configuration BCPInfrastructureRoute ServerLooking GlassTraffic GraphsLocationsIRC ServerPartners/SponsorsAboutWhat is an Internet ExchangeContactPrivacy PolicyInformation Security Policy
Toggle navigation
HomeAssociationParticipationInfrastructurePartners/SponsorsAbout
IXPManager
Status
What is an Internet ExchangeContactPrivacy PolicyInformation Security Policy
HomeAboutPrivacy Policy
Privacy policy for website
Responsible for the collection, processing and use of your personal data is
SwissIX Internet Exchange
Badenerstrasse 569
8048 Zürich
Switzerland
Rights of the data concerned: rights of access, rectification, blocking, cancellation and opposition
You have the right, upon request, to request information about the personal data stored by us free of charge and/or to request a correction, blocking or deletion. A blocking or deletion cannot take place if legal regulations prevent this.
Please contact our data protection officer at privacy@swissix.ch.
Data avoidance and data economy
In accordance with the principles of data avoidance and data economy, we only store personal data for as long as this is necessary or prescribed by the legislator.
Gathering general information
Information about access to our website is generally not collected automatically (in the form of log files). For administrative purposes, a short-term creation of log files may be necessary. In this case, the log files are then deleted. The log files are of a general nature and do not allow conclusions about your person.
If log files are created, the following data types can be collected, among other things: IP address and date.
